[Wednesday] It's been
an eventful summer.
♪ Raindrops on roses ♪
[dark cover of "My
Favorite Things" plays]
♪ And whiskers on kittens ♪
[Wednesday] I'm tied up in
a serial killer's basement.
Who said nightmares
don't come true?
♪ Bright copper kettles ♪
♪ And warm woolen mittens ♪
[Wednesday] He's under the
delusion that I'm his next victim.
♪ Brown paper packages
Tied up with strings ♪
I'll let him cherish that notion
while I explain my predicament.
♪ These are a few of
my favorite things ♪
[Wednesday] I spent my vacation
mastering my psychic ability.
All the answers were in
Goody's book of spells.
[whispering softly]
With my ability
now under control,
I set my sights on an obsession
I've had since I was six years old.
[school bell rings]
[young Wednesday] Before
dying, victim number 11
described the suspect.
[Wednesday] The
Kansas City Scalper,
America's most
elusive serial killer.
…blood everywhere.
To psychically locate him,
all I needed was an object
from one of his crime scenes.